<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Akhil Peddikuppa</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Akhil Peddikuppa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Quiz Bowl Team</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/4/quizbowlintro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/4/quizbowlintro/</guid>
      <description>What is Quiz Bowl?  Quiz Bowl is an academic competition in which two teams compete to answer questions from all areas of knowledge, including history, literature, science, fine arts, current events, pop culture, sports, and more.
   This video is from the NAQT, which is an organization that provides Quiz Bowl questions.  How does Quiz Bowl work? Quiz Bowl is unique in the sense that it is an academic competition in which you don&amp;rsquo;t take a test for, but, instead, you buzz in to answer questions, which makes tournaments an enjoyable experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Import Quizlet Decks to Anki</title>
      <link>/posts/2021/1/howtoimportquizletdeckstoanki/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021/1/howtoimportquizletdeckstoanki/</guid>
      <description>Importing decks from Quizlet into Anki is very simple. Here&amp;rsquo;s how:
Steps to Import  With Anki open, navigate to the toolbar Go to Tools &amp;gt; Add-ons Click Get Add-ons Paste 538351043 and hit OK (This installs the Quizlet Importer add-on) Next, Restart Anki Go to the Quizlet deck you want to import Copy the link, then go to Tools &amp;gt; Import from Quizlet Paste the Quizlet link, hit OK, and you&amp;rsquo;re all done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Levels of Vehicle Automation in 3 Minutes</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/5/levelsofvehicleautomation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/5/levelsofvehicleautomation/</guid>
      <description>With automation and especially automation in cars becoming more present in everyday life, it is important to know the concepts associated with the new technology that will one day be all around us.
Here are the levels of vehicle automation in 3 minutes.
Level 0: No Automation These vehicles are the normal everyday cars that are manually controlled and ones that you most likely own. Almost all cars available fall in this category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove Password Protection from a PDF on a Mac</title>
      <link>/posts/2021/1/howtoremovepasswordpdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021/1/howtoremovepasswordpdf/</guid>
      <description>Steps  Open the PDF in Preview by double-clicking it in Finder Go to File &amp;gt; Export as PDF... Remove the second .pdf and save the file There will be a dialog that asks to replace it, click Replace  That&amp;rsquo;s it. The password protection has been removed from the PDF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/12/gettingstartedwithhugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/12/gettingstartedwithhugo/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial will explain the steps needed to get started with Hugo to build a static website for your blog or portfolio.
What is Hugo? Hugo is a free and open source static site generator used by many to create blogs or portfolio websites for themselves. I myself use Hugo for this portfolio/blog site.
Step 1: Installation The easiest way to install Hugo is through Homebrew. I recommend installing Homebrew as it makes downloading apps a lot easier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Free and Professional Video-Editing Program</title>
      <link>/posts/2020/4/favoritefreevideoediting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020/4/favoritefreevideoediting/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article was updated with the release of DaVinci Resolve 17 DaVinci Resolve 17 is a video editing software that is FREE, used by professionals and packs many features that make it a great alternative to Adobe&amp;rsquo;s Creative Cloud or Apple&amp;rsquo;s Final Cut.
What is DaVinci Resolve? If you take a look at the main video-editing softwares used by professionals, you&amp;rsquo;re most likely going to see either Premiere Pro or Final Cut Pro X.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
